<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

  <FactionDef ParentName="OutlanderFactionBase">
    <defName>Russia</defName>
    <label>Cosmocratic Soviets</label>
    <description>The Cosmocratic Soviets embody the ideals of a classless society and collective ownership, forging a tightly-knit community in the stars. Their governing structure revolves around a central council, composed of representatives from various sectors such as agriculture, science, and military. This council, guided by Marxist principles, aims to achieve social equality, scientific progress, and the common good of all its members.

At the heart of their society lies the industrial machine, reminiscent of the Soviet Union's emphasis on heavy industry. The Cosmocratic Soviets have established colossal starbases and orbital platforms, bustling with the hum of machinery, where production lines churn out essential resources, advanced technologies, and the means for space exploration. These structures loom in the void, a testament to their engineering prowess and determination to conquer the cosmos.

Although the Cosmocratic Soviets strive for a utopian society, the harsh realities of survival in space have forced them to adopt pragmatic measures to maintain order. They possess a strong military presence, with a disciplined and highly trained force comprised of citizen-soldiers. These defenders of the collective are tasked with safeguarding the Cosmocratic Soviets' territories from external threats and ensuring the stability of their way of life.</description>
	<factionIconPath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/russia</factionIconPath>
	<settlementTexturePath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/russia</settlementTexturePath>
	<settlementGenerationWeight>.5</settlementGenerationWeight>
    <canSiege>true</canSiege>
    <canStageAttacks>true</canStageAttacks>
    <leaderTitle>Leader</leaderTitle>
	<factionNameMaker>RussianClan</factionNameMaker>
	<settlementNameMaker>NamerSettlementRussia</settlementNameMaker>
	<pawnSingular>Soviet</pawnSingular>
	<pawnsPlural>Soviets</pawnsPlural>
	<melaninRange>0~0.3</melaninRange>
	<xenotypeSet Inherit="False">
     <xenotypeChances>
	 <russian>999</russian>
     </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
	<colorSpectrum>
      <li>(1, 1, 1)</li>
    </colorSpectrum>
    <maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>9999</maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>
    <configurationListOrderPriority>10</configurationListOrderPriority>
  </FactionDef>
  
  <FactionDef ParentName="OutlanderFactionBase">
    <defName>England</defName>
    <label>Britannia Dominion</label>
    <description>The Britannia Dominion is a vast interstellar empire, encompassing diverse colonies and territories across the Rimworld. Led by a monarch, who holds a ceremonial position as the symbol of national unity and continuity, the Dominion is governed by a parliamentary system, blending constitutional monarchy with representative democracy.

Technological innovation is a cornerstone of the Britannia Dominion's society. Their scientists and engineers push the boundaries of knowledge, developing advanced technologies that fuel their spacefaring capabilities. Their starships, equipped with state-of-the-art propulsion systems and advanced weaponry, project the Dominion's power and influence across the cosmos.

Deeply rooted in a legacy of exploration, the Britannia Dominion remains committed to expanding its dominion over new frontiers. They establish colonies on distant planets, establishing outposts and mining operations to exploit the resources of the Rimworld. Their explorers, driven by a sense of adventure and discovery, map uncharted territories, seeking out new knowledge and hidden wonders.

The Dominion's society is built upon a foundation of social and cultural diversity. Embracing a multicultural ethos, they celebrate the contributions of various ethnicities and backgrounds, fostering an environment of tolerance and respect. Art, literature, and scientific research flourish within their society, as they value both intellectual pursuits and the preservation of their historical heritage.</description>
	<factionIconPath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/england</factionIconPath>
	<settlementTexturePath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/england</settlementTexturePath>
	<settlementGenerationWeight>.5</settlementGenerationWeight>
    <canSiege>true</canSiege>
    <canStageAttacks>true</canStageAttacks>
    <leaderTitle>Monarch</leaderTitle>
	<factionNameMaker>EnglandClan</factionNameMaker>
	<settlementNameMaker>NamerSettlementEngland</settlementNameMaker>
	<pawnSingular>British</pawnSingular>
	<pawnsPlural>British</pawnsPlural>
	<melaninRange>0~0.5</melaninRange>
	<xenotypeSet Inherit="False">
     <xenotypeChances>
	 <england>999</england>
     </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
	<colorSpectrum>
      <li>(1, 1, 1)</li>
    </colorSpectrum>
    <maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>9999</maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>
    <configurationListOrderPriority>10</configurationListOrderPriority>
  </FactionDef>
  
  <FactionDef ParentName="OutlanderFactionBase">
    <defName>France</defName>
    <label>Republic of Gallia</label>
    <description>The Republic of Gallia stands as a bastion of democratic ideals within the cosmos. Governed by a president and a representative assembly, the nation's leadership is elected by its citizens, ensuring a government that reflects the will of the people. Gallia embraces the principles of liberty, equality, and fraternity, promoting a society that values individual rights and collective well-being.

Gallia's culture is steeped in culinary arts, literature, and philosophy, celebrating creativity and intellectual pursuits. The faction fosters an environment where artistic expression flourishes, and scientific breakthroughs are encouraged. Their scientists and scholars delve into research, advancing knowledge in various fields and pushing the boundaries of human understanding.</description>
	<factionIconPath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/france</factionIconPath>
	<settlementTexturePath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/france</settlementTexturePath>
	<settlementGenerationWeight>.5</settlementGenerationWeight>
    <canSiege>true</canSiege>
    <canStageAttacks>true</canStageAttacks>
    <leaderTitle>Emperor</leaderTitle>
	<factionNameMaker>FranceClan</factionNameMaker>
	<settlementNameMaker>NamerSettlementFrance</settlementNameMaker>
	<pawnSingular>Gallian</pawnSingular>
	<pawnsPlural>Gallians</pawnsPlural>
	<melaninRange>0~1</melaninRange>
	<xenotypeSet Inherit="False">
     <xenotypeChances>
	 <france>999</france>
     </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
	<colorSpectrum>
      <li>(1, 1, 1)</li>
    </colorSpectrum>
    <maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>9999</maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>
    <configurationListOrderPriority>10</configurationListOrderPriority>
  </FactionDef>
  
  <FactionDef ParentName="OutlanderFactionBase">
    <defName>Spain</defName>
    <label>Solarian Empire</label>
    <description>The Solarian Empire is a decentralized confederation of autonomous regions, each with its own distinct culture and identity. These regions come together under the banner of the Empire, united by shared ideals of liberty, self-determination, and a deep reverence for exploration and discovery.

The Solarian Empire places great importance on fostering cultural diversity and intellectual pursuits. Art and literature flourish within their society, celebrating the richness of human expression. The medical knowledge they possess is beyond the rest.

With a rich history of exploration and seafaring, the Solarian Empire takes to the stars with a spirit of adventure and discovery. Their explorers and pioneers, driven by a longing for new horizons, venture forth into the unknown, eager to uncover the mysteries of the universe.</description>
	<factionIconPath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/spain</factionIconPath>
	<settlementTexturePath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/spain</settlementTexturePath>
	<settlementGenerationWeight>.5</settlementGenerationWeight>
    <canSiege>true</canSiege>
    <canStageAttacks>true</canStageAttacks>
    <leaderTitle>General</leaderTitle>
	<factionNameMaker>SpainClan</factionNameMaker>
	<settlementNameMaker>NamerSettlementSpain</settlementNameMaker>
	<pawnSingular>Solarian</pawnSingular>
	<pawnsPlural>Solarians</pawnsPlural>
	<melaninRange>0.2~0.6</melaninRange>
	<xenotypeSet Inherit="False">
     <xenotypeChances>
	 <spain>999</spain>
     </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
	<colorSpectrum>
      <li>(1, 1, 1)</li>
    </colorSpectrum>
    <maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>9999</maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>
    <configurationListOrderPriority>10</configurationListOrderPriority>
  </FactionDef>

  <FactionDef ParentName="OutlanderRoughBase">
    <defName>Germany</defName>
    <label>Iron Reich</label>
    <description>The Iron Reich operates under a strict hierarchical structure, with an authoritarian leadership at its core. A single, charismatic figurehead known as the Führer commands the faction, surrounded by a loyal inner circle of military strategists, scientists, and administrators. They believe in the supremacy of their nation and the relentless pursuit of power and order.

Their industrial might fuels the production of war materiel, allowing them to project dominance in the Rimworld. Their bases are fortified with imposing architecture and fortified walls, echoing the disciplined and unwavering spirit of their predecessors.

Driven by a thirst for expansion and conquest, the Iron Reich pursues an aggressive expansionist policy. Their military forces, consisting of highly trained soldiers and formidable war machines, are deployed to enforce their will upon others.</description>
	<factionIconPath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/germany</factionIconPath>
	<settlementTexturePath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/germany</settlementTexturePath>
	<settlementGenerationWeight>.5</settlementGenerationWeight>
    <canSiege>true</canSiege>
    <canStageAttacks>true</canStageAttacks>
    <leaderTitle>Fuhrer</leaderTitle>
	<factionNameMaker>GermanyClan</factionNameMaker>
	<settlementNameMaker>NamerSettlementGermany</settlementNameMaker>
	<pawnSingular>Stahl</pawnSingular>
	<melaninRange>0~0.3</melaninRange>
	<pawnsPlural>Stahls</pawnsPlural>
	<xenotypeSet Inherit="False">
     <xenotypeChances>
	 <germany>999</germany>
     </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
	<colorSpectrum>
      <li>(1, 1, 1)</li>
    </colorSpectrum>
    <maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>9999</maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>
    <configurationListOrderPriority>10</configurationListOrderPriority>
  </FactionDef>
  
    <FactionDef ParentName="OutlanderFactionBase">
    <defName>Japan</defName>
    <label>Yamato Shogunate</label>
    <description>The Yamato Shogunate is led by a revered Shogun, a central figure embodying strength, wisdom, and the ancestral spirit of the empire. The Shogunate's leadership is supported by a council of advisors and influential feudal lords, forming a hierarchical structure that upholds the traditions and values of ancient Japan.

Technological innovation thrives within the Yamato Shogunate. Their technological advancements blend seamlessly with their traditional aesthetics, resulting in a unique fusion of modernity and honor.

The Shogunate places great importance on martial prowess and disciplined warfare. Their warriors, known as Bushido Knights, are highly trained and skilled in a variety of combat styles, combining traditional swordsmanship with advanced weaponry and martial arts. Loyalty, honor, and self-sacrifice are deeply ingrained in their code of conduct.

The Yamato Shogunate's society is steeped in a rich tapestry of traditions, ceremonies, and cultural practices. Their arts, literature, and performing arts showcase a deep reverence for their historical heritage and the pursuit of beauty. Zen philosophy and the principles of harmony, simplicity, and balance permeate every aspect of their society.</description>
	<factionIconPath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/japan</factionIconPath>
	<settlementTexturePath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/japan</settlementTexturePath>
	<settlementGenerationWeight>.5</settlementGenerationWeight>
    <canSiege>true</canSiege>
    <canStageAttacks>true</canStageAttacks>
    <leaderTitle>Shogun</leaderTitle>
	<factionNameMaker>JapanClan</factionNameMaker>
	<settlementNameMaker>NamerSettlementJapan</settlementNameMaker>
	<pawnSingular>Nipon</pawnSingular>
	<pawnsPlural>Nipons</pawnsPlural>
	<melaninRange>0~0.1</melaninRange>
	<xenotypeSet Inherit="False">
     <xenotypeChances>
	 <japan>999</japan>
     </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
	<colorSpectrum>
      <li>(1, 1, 1)</li>
    </colorSpectrum>
    <maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>9999</maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>
    <configurationListOrderPriority>10</configurationListOrderPriority>
  </FactionDef>
  
    <FactionDef ParentName="OutlanderFactionBase">
    <defName>Usa</defName>
    <label>United Star Coalition</label>
    <description>The United Star Coalition upholds the principles of democracy, with a President serving as the head of state and a representative congress shaping the nation's policies. The Coalition values individual liberty, equality, and the pursuit of happiness, fostering a society that encourages personal freedoms and opportunities for all its citizens.

Technological advancement plays a pivotal role within the United Star Coalition. The United Star Coalition embraces cultural diversity, celebrating the contributions of people from different backgrounds, ethnicities, and beliefs. They tend to impose their idea of peace on the Rimworld.

The Coalition's military forces, known as the Stellar Guardians, are highly trained and equipped with advanced weaponry and defensive systems. Their primary objective is to protect the Coalition's interests, safeguard colonies, and maintain peace within the Rimworld. The Stellar Guardians are the ones in charge of the protection of the Nation.</description>
	<factionIconPath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/usa</factionIconPath>
	<settlementTexturePath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/usa</settlementTexturePath>
	<settlementGenerationWeight>.5</settlementGenerationWeight>
    <canSiege>true</canSiege>
    <canStageAttacks>true</canStageAttacks>
    <leaderTitle>President</leaderTitle>
	<factionNameMaker>UsaClan</factionNameMaker>
	<settlementNameMaker>NamerSettlementUsa</settlementNameMaker>
	<pawnSingular>Star</pawnSingular>
	<pawnsPlural>Stars</pawnsPlural>
	<melaninRange>0~1</melaninRange>
	<xenotypeSet Inherit="False">
     <xenotypeChances>
	 <usa>999</usa>
     </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
	<colorSpectrum>
      <li>(1, 1, 1)</li>
    </colorSpectrum>
    <maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>9999</maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>
    <configurationListOrderPriority>10</configurationListOrderPriority>
  </FactionDef>
  
    <FactionDef ParentName="OutlanderFactionBase">
    <defName>Italy</defName>
    <label>Nova Impero</label>
    <description>Nova Impero is governed by a High Consul, who leads the faction with wisdom and authority. The Consul's rule is supported by a council of noble families, representing the diverse regions and traditions of the Italian heritage. Their governance combines elements of meritocracy and aristocracy, valuing expertise and noble lineage.

Technological innovation is a focal point within Nova Impero. They excel in the fields of engineering, architecture, and scientific research, combining cutting-edge technology with a flair for aesthetics.

The faction embraces its rich cultural heritage, with a focus on arts. They celebrate the contributions of renowned artists, poets, and philosophers, fostering an environment where creativity and intellectual pursuits gaining renown for the Nation. Nova Impero's cities are adorned with grand architecture, blending ancient aesthetics with futuristic design.

While Nova Impero values their traditions, they are not confined by the past. They adapt to the challenges of the Rimworld with strategic pragmatism, blending their cultural legacy with technological advancements. Their colonists and engineers exhibit resourcefulness and adaptability, employing their ingenuity to overcome obstacles and thrive in the unforgiving cosmos.</description>
	<factionIconPath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/italy</factionIconPath>
	<settlementTexturePath>World/WorldObjects/Expanding/italy</settlementTexturePath>
	<settlementGenerationWeight>.5</settlementGenerationWeight>
    <canSiege>true</canSiege>
    <canStageAttacks>true</canStageAttacks>
    <leaderTitle>Emperor</leaderTitle>
	<factionNameMaker>ItalyClan</factionNameMaker>
	<settlementNameMaker>NamerSettlementItaly</settlementNameMaker>
	<pawnSingular>Novan</pawnSingular>
	<pawnsPlural>Novans</pawnsPlural>
	<melaninRange>0.1~0.5</melaninRange>
	<xenotypeSet Inherit="False">
     <xenotypeChances>
	 <italy>999</italy>
     </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
	<colorSpectrum>
      <li>(1, 1, 1)</li>
    </colorSpectrum>
    <maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>9999</maxConfigurableAtWorldCreation>
    <configurationListOrderPriority>10</configurationListOrderPriority>
  </FactionDef>  
</Defs>